So well for.
Your record transmitter microphone going.
I can't figure out where to connect. I
know I have to connect. But where this is.
Why not a store and get more information.
By the way how things are
going in school. Oh OK.
But school here isn't like I was back in
Morristown But you know maybe school is
like your radio.
This oscillator will do its work well
but as you said you still have to fit it
in so it can work with all the other five
hundred what you're driving at. Dad But I
don't think I ever will fit in here on.
I'm different from the guys
in this town but as far as
that goes fail everybody's different.
That's what makes people interesting.
Maybe you know.